{
  "title": "Networking Knowledge Assessments",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "q1",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which of the following is not a downside of fully meshing BGP peers?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Configuration overheads"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Poor scaling"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Node isolation"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Management overheads"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Node isolation."
    },
    {
      "id": "q2",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Without route reflectors or confederations, how do IBGP peers have to be organized in a Transit AS?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "IBGP peers must use OSPF as an IGP."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "IBGP peers must be peered with EBGP peers."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "IBGP peers must be limited in numbers."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "IBGP peers must be fully meshed with each other."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: IBGP peers must be fully meshed with each other.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q3",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "What kind of routing protocol runs within an organization's or enterprise's autonomous system?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "EBGP"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "IGP"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "IBGP"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "TCP"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: IGP."
    },
    {
      "id": "q4",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "What is the name for the 'standardized multi-stage process' used by BGP peers to establish a peer relationship?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "TCP connection establishment"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "TCP session establishment"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Peering state logic"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Finite State Machine"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Finite State Machine."
    },
    {
      "id": "q5",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Approximately how many routing table entries does an Internet BGP router currently hold?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "100,000"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "500,008"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Inmillion"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "1@million"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Inmillion."
    },
    {
      "id": "q6",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which of the following is not a true description of BGP?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "BGP 'hides' ISP infrastructure."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "BGP permits highly flexible routing policy."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "BGPadvertises any intra-AS topology changes."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "BGPis a selective routing protocol."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: BGPadvertises any intra-AS topology changes.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q7",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "What's another name for a 'path attribute'?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Variable"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Link"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Table entry"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Metric"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Metric."
    },
    {
      "id": "q8",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "With confederations, Member ASs are connected by BGP peers running which protocol?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Intraconfederation EBGP"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Intraconfederation BGP"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Interconfederation EBGP"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Interconfederation BGP"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Intraconfederation EBGP."
    },
    {
      "id": "q9",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "What would a BGP peer router do if it received no Keepalive message from its peer router within the required timeframe?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Send a Notification message to ask if the peer is 'alive'."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "End the BGP peering."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Wait 60 seconds more."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Move to the 'OpenSent'' state."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: End the BGP peering.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q10",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which of the following statements is correct?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "BGP is the only routing protocol used to connect autonomous systems."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "BGP is a very popular inter-AS routing protocol, but OSPF can also be used."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "There are several routing protocols used to connect autonomous systems,"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: BGP is the only routing protocol used to connect autonomous systems.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q11",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Why do you need to be careful using BGP 'redistribute' statements?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Because they can create network loops."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Because they will not share private addresses/prefixes."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Because they will share the entire set of local IGP prefixes if you don't use some form"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Because they will share the entire set of local IGP prefixes if you don't use some form."
    },
    {
      "id": "q12",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "autonomous system. Which transport protocol is used by BGP to establish peering sessions?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "BITP"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "UDP"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "TTB"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "TcP"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: TcP."
    },
    {
      "id": "q13",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Internal BGP can be used to create what kind of distributed system, capable of aggregating and forwarding IP traffic in bulk?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Packet backbone network"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Data center"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Ethernet switch"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Transit AS"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Transit AS."
    },
    {
      "id": "q14",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which statement is not a true statement about the BGP state model?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "The state model is called a Finite State Machine."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Each state has a direct path to the 'Idle' state."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "There are time duration dependencies for all state transitions."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The state machine has six states."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: There are time duration dependencies for all state transitions.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q15",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which two statements are used to instruct a router to share prefixes?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Network and announce"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Share and redistribute"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Share and announce"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Network and redistribute"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Network and redistribute."
    },
    {
      "id": "q16",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which of these four qualities is not typically used to describe BGP?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Stable"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Reliable"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Low latency"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Scalable"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Low latency."
    },
    {
      "id": "q17",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which is the only path attribute to be added individually by a subsequent RFC to RFC4271?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Multi Exit Discriminator"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "AIGP"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Weight"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Local Preference"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: AIGP."
    },
    {
      "id": "q18",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "What is the main purpose of path attributes?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Tocommunicate Link layer information."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Todifferentiate between IBGP and EBGP-connected peers."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Toenablea BGP router to select the best path to a network prefix."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Tocommunicate how many BGP peers each BGP router has."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Toenablea BGP router to select the best path to a network prefix.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q19",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "How do BGP peers exchange path attribute information?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Using the BGP-MU messaging protocol."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Using Notification messages."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Using Update messages."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Using the BGP-MP messaging protocol."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Using Update messages.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q20",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "The path attribute 'Origin type' prefers what type of paths?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Paths marked with an 'i' at the end of their AS path description."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Paths from EBGP peers."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Locally imported paths."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Paths with a low number of AS hops."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Locally imported paths.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q21",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "In Accumulated IGP ('AIGP'), what is being accumulated?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Metrics"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "MEDs"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "AS hops"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "EBGP peers"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Metrics."
    },
    {
      "id": "q22",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "What does the Network Layer Reachability Information (NLRI) consist of?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Prefix and Next Hop"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Length and Prefix"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Length and Path"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Next Hop and Length"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Length and Prefix."
    },
    {
      "id": "q23",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "During the 'Internal/External tiebreaker step, which type of routes will BGP remove from consideration?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "All routes received via iBGP"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "All routes with an AS Hop count of more than one."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "All routes received from another BGP peer."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "All routes received through an Update message."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: All routes received via iBGP."
    },
    {
      "id": "q24",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which of the following does not exist in a modern network that uses switches rather than hubs.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Collisions"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Broadcasts"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Bridging table"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "VLANs"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Collisions."
    },
    {
      "id": "q25",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "What field in an Ethernet header comes between the Destination Address field and the Type field?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Time To Live"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Source Address"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "FCS"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Type of Service"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Source Address."
    },
    {
      "id": "q26",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "When a broadcast is sent to a switch, the switch will forward it to......?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "all interfaces connected to switches"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "no interfaces"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "all interfaces in all VLANs"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "all interfaces in the same VLAN"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: all interfaces connected to switches."
    },
    {
      "id": "q27",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "A bridge builds up a bridging table by examining the _____ of incoming frames?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Source IP address"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Destination IP address"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Destination MAC address"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Source MAC address"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Source MAC address."
    },
    {
      "id": "q28",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Bridges and switches increase the number of collision domains in a network.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "True"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "False"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: True."
    },
    {
      "id": "q29",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which of the following OSI Layers does Ethernet operate on?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Session"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Network"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Data Link"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Presentation"
        },
        {
          "id": "E",
          "text": "Application"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Data Link."
    },
    {
      "id": "q30",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "E-Line creates a virtual (i) connection between sites and E-LAN creates a virtual (ii) connection between sites. Fill in the two blanks with the correct terms.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "(i) point-to-multipoint, (ii) multipoint-to-point"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "(i) point-to-point, (ii) multipoint-to-multipoint"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "(i) multipoint-to-multipoint, (ii) point-to-point"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "(i) rooted-to-multipoint, (ii) multipoint-to-point"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: (i) point-to-point, (ii) multipoint-to-multipoint."
    },
    {
      "id": "q31",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Typically, switches process frames (i) whereas bridges process frames (ii) . Fill in the two blanks with the correct terms.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "(i) in hardware, (ii) in software"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "(i) based on QoS, (ii) based on MAC addresses"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "(i) at layer two, (ii) at layer three"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "(i) in software, (ii) in hardware"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: (i) in hardware, (ii) in software."
    },
    {
      "id": "q32",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "At which speed does an 10@@Base-LX1@ Ethernet connection operate?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "1000 bit/s"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "10 Gbit/s"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "100 Mbit/s"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "1Gbit/s"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 1Gbit/s."
    },
    {
      "id": "q33",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "How many bits are there in an Ethernet address?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "24"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "32"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "48"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "64"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 48."
    },
    {
      "id": "q34",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Can different interfaces on the same switch be assigned to different VLANs?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Yes."
    },
    {
      "id": "q35",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Do VLANs allow different networks to connect to the same switches?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "No"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Yes"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Yes."
    },
    {
      "id": "q36",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Where in an Ethernet frame are the VLAN tags inserted?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "After the Source Address field and before the Type field."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Directly after the Destination Address field."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Inthe Data field."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Inthe Type field, just after the Source Address field."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: After the Source Address field and before the Type field.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q37",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "What is the name of the main standard for VLAN tagging?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "IEEE 802.1Q"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "IEEE 806.9"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "IEEE 802.1ad"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "IEEE 8@6.Q in Asia and IEEE 802.1Q in the rest of the world."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: IEEE 802.1Q."
    },
    {
      "id": "q38",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which VLAN tagging operations exist?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Push, Switch, Swap"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Pop, Rock, Punk"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Delete, Replace, Forward"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Push, Pop, Swap"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Push, Pop, Swap."
    },
    {
      "id": "q39",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "What is the part of a double-tagged frame called that contains two VLAN tags?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "VLAN tag stack"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Combined tag or C-tag"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "VLAN tag bundle"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "VLAN tag pyramid"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: VLAN tag stack."
    },
    {
      "id": "q40",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "What are switch ports configured as ina VLAN?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Trunk ports or Passive ports"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Access ports or Dedicated ports"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Access ports or Trunk ports"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Dedicated ports"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Access ports or Trunk ports."
    },
    {
      "id": "q41",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "What are the outer and inner VLAN tags also called?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Switch tag / S-tag and Customer tag / C-tag"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Customer tag / C-tag and VLAN ID tag / VID-tag"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Service tag / S-tag and Customer tag / C-tag"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Switch tag / S-tag and Priority Code Point tag / PCP-tag"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Service tag / S-tag and Customer tag / C-tag."
    },
    {
      "id": "q42",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which is true regarding an Ethernet Spanning Tree?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "It eliminates broadcasts."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "It loops frames to add redundancy to the network."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "It is used to separate VLANs."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "There is only one active path between any two points."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: There is only one active path between any two points.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q43",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "MSTP is superior to STP and RSTP on three points and inferior on one. Which is the latter?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Flawless interaction with legacy bridges"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Highly scalable"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Load balancing"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Traffic engineering"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Flawless interaction with legacy bridges."
    },
    {
      "id": "q44",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which connection type does NOT exist for RSTP?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Edge"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Dedicated"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Shared"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Point-to-Point"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Dedicated."
    },
    {
      "id": "q45",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Where in the Ethernet frame is the information encapsulated on which the port role selections are based?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "In the Type field, just after the Source Address field."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "In the Data field."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "In the Preamble field."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Directly after the Destination Address field."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: In the Data field.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q46",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "What is the name of the messages Ethernet switches running spanning tree protocols send to each other?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "BID"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "ISL"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Root Message"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "BPDU"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: BPDU."
    },
    {
      "id": "q47",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which is an STP port role?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Root port"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Listening port"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Dedicated port"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "LACP port"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Root port."
    },
    {
      "id": "q48",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which kind of port is always in forwarding state?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Root bridge port"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Root port"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Designated port"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Alternate port"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Root bridge port."
    },
    {
      "id": "q49",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "RSTP includes two port roles not defined in STP. Backup is one of them, which is the other?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Dedicated"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Root"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Alternate"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Designated"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Alternate."
    },
    {
      "id": "q50",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which of these applications is not affected so much by delay?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "File transfer"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Video over IP"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Online trading"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "VoIP"
        },
        {
          "id": "E",
          "text": "Online gaming"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: File transfer."
    },
    {
      "id": "q51",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which of these methods is not a way of increasing capacity in a network?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Increase the number of switches"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Upgrade all fast Ethernet links / cables to gigabit Ethernet links / cables"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Increase the number of routers"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Implement proper queuing mechanisms in the routers"
        },
        {
          "id": "E",
          "text": "Increase the number of links / cables"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Implement proper queuing mechanisms in the routers."
    },
    {
      "id": "q52",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "What does QoS stands for?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Queuing over Signaling"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Queuing over SIGTRAN"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Quality of Signaling"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Quality of Service"
        },
        {
          "id": "E",
          "text": "Queuing or Scheduling"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Quality of Service."
    },
    {
      "id": "q53",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which of the following applications is an example of a \"real-time\" application?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "File Transfer (FTP)"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "VoIP"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Web browsing"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Movie download"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: VoIP."
    },
    {
      "id": "q54",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "For what purpose was Internet traditionally used?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "To watch videos"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "To play online games"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "To make phone calls"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "To transfer information from one location to another"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: To transfer information from one location to another."
    },
    {
      "id": "q55",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Jitter is the metering of packets due to a service level agreement with the customer.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "True"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "False"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: False."
    },
    {
      "id": "q56",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which statement or statements are true regarding DiffServ architecture?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "So Routers at the edge of a DiffServ domain mark packets according to the domain QoS policy"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "DiffServ allows for end to end bandwidth reservation"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Each router within a DiffServ domain takes independent QoS decision when forwarding a packet"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Each router within a DiffServ domain needs to classify incoming packets to provide proper QoS"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: So Routers at the edge of a DiffServ domain mark packets according to the domain QoS policy."
    },
    {
      "id": "q57",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "handling Where is the DiffServ (Differentiated Services) value defined?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Ina label inserted after the IP header"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "In the IP header of a packet"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "In each router's forwarding table"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "In the content of a packet"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: In the IP header of a packet."
    },
    {
      "id": "q58",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "When classifying traffic, which type of identifier will classify a packet based only on the value of the DSCP?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Multi-Field Classifier"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Token Bucket"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "BA identifier"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: BA identifier."
    },
    {
      "id": "q59",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "In PWFQ scheduling, which of the following factors is taken into consideration first when deciding on which queue should be served first?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Force"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Priority"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Queue number"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Weight"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Priority."
    },
    {
      "id": "q60",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Even if there is plenty of bandwidth available, which of the following might still cause problems in the network?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Delay"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Jitter"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Throughput"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Loss"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Jitter."
    },
    {
      "id": "q61",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "WFQ uses what to manage division of bandwidth between queues?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Force"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Queue number"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Weight"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Priority"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Weight."
    },
    {
      "id": "q62",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "How many different types of traffic does DiffServ allow?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "8"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "16"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "32"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "64"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 64."
    },
    {
      "id": "q63",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "When using RED as a traffic congestion avoidance mechanism, all the packets trying to enter the queue will be dropped when:",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "The queue depth reaches the minimum occupancy threshold."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "The queue depth reaches a point where drop probability is 10@."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "The queue depth reaches a point where drop probability is 1."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The queue depth reaches the maximum occupancy threshold."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: The queue depth reaches a point where drop probability is 1.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q64",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "A port has been configured with PWFQ scheduler for 4 queues and a maximum rate of 4 Mbit/s. Queue 0 has been configured with a priority 1 and a weight of 52. Queue 1 has been configured with priority 1 and weight 50. Queues 3 and 4 both have a priority of 2 but weights of 30 and 70 respectively. At this given moment the port receives the following traffic pattern: No traffic for queue 0. 1 Mb of traffic for queue 1. 3 Mb for queue 3. 2.5 Mb for queue 4. How much traffic will be transmitted from Queue 1?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "0 Mb"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "0. 3 Mb"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "0.5 Mb"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "1Mb"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 1Mb."
    },
    {
      "id": "q65",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "same class How many QoS classes are supported by the Ethernet standard?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "3"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "8"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "64"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "256"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 8."
    },
    {
      "id": "q66",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "TCAs are agreements between what?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Nodes not in any DS domain."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Boundary nodes with the same defined PHBs and DSCP-to-PHB mappings."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Boundary nodes."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "All DS enabled nodes."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Boundary nodes.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q67",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which of the following classes of PHB in DiffServ is the higher priority QoS class out of the following?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "EF"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "DF"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "AF1"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "AF2"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: EF."
    },
    {
      "id": "q68",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "If using PWFQ, when the priorities of all the queues are the same, then the schedulers behave like?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "PFQ"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "PQ"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "PWQ"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "WFQ"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: WFQ."
    },
    {
      "id": "q69",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which one of the following statements is true about queuing?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "A queue is infinite in length."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Queues are always emptied in a round-robin fashion, one packet from each queue at a time."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "It will only work properly if the flow of traffic is bursty."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Packets arriving are put in different queues in a round-robin fashion, depending on which"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: It will only work properly if the flow of traffic is bursty.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q70",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "arrive first. Why do many IP networks use a 'meshed' topology?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "To avoid using expensive routers."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "To provide resiliency and additional capacity."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "To reduce the number of IP addresses needed."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "To avoid loops forming."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: To provide resiliency and additional capacity.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q71",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "From where did the physical Internet originate?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "The DECNET in the USA."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "The ISOnet in the USA."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "The ARPAnet in the USA."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The IEEEnet in the USA."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: The ARPAnet in the USA.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q72",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "In which decade was the World Wide Web (HTML, URLs etc.) founded?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "1960s"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "1970s"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "1980s"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "1990s"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 1990s."
    },
    {
      "id": "q73",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "The TCP/IP model consists of the Application, Network, Link and which other layer?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Transport"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Data"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Routing"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Internet"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Transport."
    },
    {
      "id": "q74",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which type of network element comprises much of the central fabric of the Internet?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Database"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Router"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Smartphone"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Base station"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Router."
    },
    {
      "id": "q75",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which of the following is a true statement?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "IP can only be used for Enterprise networks."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "IP is a modern protocol developed specifically to support 21st century applications."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "IP is a suite of networking protocols."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "IP connects users to services over networks such as the Internet."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: IP connects users to services over networks such as the Internet.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q76",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "Which is a true statement about using IPv4 and IPv6 in the same network?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "It is possible only if 128-bit IPv4 addressing is used."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "It is not possible - you must use one or the other, but not both."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "It is possible for both to co-exist."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "It is possible for both to co-exist only if all network routers are provided by the same"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: It is possible for both to co-exist.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q77",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — BGP Overview",
      "question": "vendor. Before IP networks were established as multiservice networks ('One IP network'), how were networks built?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Individual networks were built using systems from only one vendor each."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "All traffic types used Asynchronous Transfer Mode (ATM) networks."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Individual networks were built for each traffic type."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "All traffic types used Frame Relay networks."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Individual networks were built for each traffic type.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q78",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — TCP/IP Model and Transport Layer",
      "question": "Why does the Border Gateway Protocol use TCP?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Because TCP is the fastest choice."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Because TCP is the more bandwidth-efficient choice."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Because TCP guarantees data integrity."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Because TCP is well suited to 'send and hope' applications."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Because TCP guarantees data integrity.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q79",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — TCP/IP Model and Transport Layer",
      "question": "Which of the following datagram types has a header and a trailer?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "An Ethernet frame."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "An IP packet."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "AUDP segment."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "A TCP segment"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: An Ethernet frame.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q80",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — TCP/IP Model and Transport Layer",
      "question": "What are Application port numbers used for?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "They are used by Applications to specify the use of TCP or UDP."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "They are used by Transport protocols to direct datagrams to the correct Application."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "They are interpreted by the Network layer to apply quality of service treatments."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "They are used by the Network layer to determine whether to drop packets."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: They are used by Transport protocols to direct datagrams to the correct Application.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q81",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — TCP/IP Model and Transport Layer",
      "question": "If the TCP transport protocol is used when the end-to-end network is suffering from a relatively high number of bit errors, what could you do to try to increase throughput while maintaining data integrity?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Increase Window size."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Decrease Window size."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Use the BGP transport protocol instead of TCP."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Use the UDP transport protocol instead of TCP."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Use the BGP transport protocol instead of TCP.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q82",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — TCP/IP Model and Transport Layer",
      "question": "Which of the following are the names for the four layers in the TCP/IP model, from 'top' to 'bottom'?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Application, Transport, Network, Link"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Application, TCP, Data, Link"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Application, Transport, Network, Transmission"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Application, TCP, IP, Link"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Application, Transport, Network, Link."
    },
    {
      "id": "q83",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — TCP/IP Model and Transport Layer",
      "question": "Which standards body is responsible for Internet standards?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "The Internet Standards Forum."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "The Internet Engineering Forum."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "The Internet Engineering Task Force."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The Internet Protocol Task Force."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: The Internet Engineering Task Force.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q84",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — TCP/IP Model and Transport Layer",
      "question": "Why does the Network Time Protocol use UDP?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Because UDP has unique header fields specifically for network timing purposes."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Because speed is the most important requirement."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Because UDP is always prioritized for forwarding by routers."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Because data integrity is the most important requirement."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Because speed is the most important requirement.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q85",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — TCP/IP Model and Transport Layer",
      "question": "Which phrase represents the UDP transport strategy?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "'Send and check'."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "'Send and resend'."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "'Send and hope'"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "'Send and confirm'."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 'Send and hope'."
    },
    {
      "id": "q86",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "Which of the following is a correct statement?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Private IP addresses use 24-bit length addresses."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "The network 1@.x.x.x is not a Private IP address, where x = @ to 255."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Private IP addresses are not routable externally."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Private IP addresses do not use subnet masks."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Private IP addresses are not routable externally.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q87",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "How long is an IPv4 address and what order are the two parts of the address represented, left to right?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "16 bits, network part then host part"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "30 bits, host part then network part"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "32 bits, host part then network part"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "32 bits, network part then host part"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 32 bits, network part then host part."
    },
    {
      "id": "q88",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "Which of the following is not a technique to maximize available address space?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "IP version 6"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Private IP address space"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Using subnet masks"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Classless Inter-Domain Routing"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Using subnet masks."
    },
    {
      "id": "q89",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "Which of these is a Class B network address?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "100.23.16.129"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "212.34.16.11"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "70.12.3.8"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "190.155.63.0"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 190.155.63.0."
    },
    {
      "id": "q90",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "If an ISP is assigned the network address 202.100.0.0/16, which of the following subnets could be assigned to a customer of the ISP?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "35.100.0.0/18"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "198.100.30.0/28"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "202.100.192.0/18"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "202.100.0.0/15"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 202.100.192.0/18."
    },
    {
      "id": "q91",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "If you wanted to create subnets from a Class B address, what is the minimum length subnet mask you could use?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "15"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "16"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "17"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "18"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 17."
    },
    {
      "id": "q92",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "You can decide which Class (A, B, C) a classful network address is by inspecting which octet (left to right)?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "First"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Second"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Third"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Fourth"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: First."
    },
    {
      "id": "q93",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "When you apply a subnet mask to an IP address, what logical function is performed?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "NOR"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "AND"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "XOR"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "OR"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: AND."
    },
    {
      "id": "q94",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "In which part of an IP network will you normally find the highest throughput capacity routers?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "The edge"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "The network operations center"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "The access"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The core"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: The core."
    },
    {
      "id": "q95",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "Which of these answers represents two link state routing protocols?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "RIP, BGP"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "IS-IS, OSPF"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "IS-IS, BGP"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "RIP, OSPF"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: IS-IS, OSPF."
    },
    {
      "id": "q96",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "A routing table entry includes a network address, a next hop address, and what else?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "A port or interface identifier."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "An up/down status identifier for the link to the next hop."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "A routing protocol identifier."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "An IP address for the outgoing port."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: A port or interface identifier.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q97",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "route lookup. In an IP network, is the path from A to B always the same as from B to A but in reverse?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Only if the path is an even number of hops."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Yes, except after a link or node failure happens."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: No."
    },
    {
      "id": "q98",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "What type of routers are used in 'the cloud'?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Physical"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Edge"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Core"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Virtual"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Virtual."
    },
    {
      "id": "q99",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "IP Routing determines which one of the following?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "How much capacity is available in a network for transmitting data."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "What link speeds are used between routers in a network."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Which applications can be used over the network."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The path data follows when transmitted from source to destination."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: The path data follows when transmitted from source to destination.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q100",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Addressing",
      "question": "Which of these factors is not a primary routing protocol characteristic?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Routing loop avoidance."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "How route selection is determined."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "How the routing protocol scales with network size."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "How quality of service (QoS) can be delivered."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: How quality of service (QoS) can be delivered.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q101",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "Why is quick convergence a positive characteristic for a routing protocol?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Because slow convergence creates much larger routing tables."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Because quick convergence reduces the likelihood of node and link failures."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Because during the time a network is not converged, the routing process may have"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Because during the time a network is not converged, the routing process may have."
    },
    {
      "id": "q102",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "too. What is a common reason for loops forming in IP networks?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Routing table updates being affected by bit errors in transmission between nodes."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Routing tables not reflecting the true state of the network topology."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Badly made cables."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Routing protocol computation errors."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Routing tables not reflecting the true state of the network topology.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q103",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "What is/are the missing word(s) in the following sentence? Routing convergence happens when a set of routers in a network all share the same information about the network in which they operate.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Protocol"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Pre-calculated path"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Alternate route"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Topology"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Topology."
    },
    {
      "id": "q104",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "What mechanism exists to provide protection against link and node failures, before network convergence occurs?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Fast reroute"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Route summarization"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Border routing"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Quality of Service"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Fast reroute."
    },
    {
      "id": "q105",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "Which of the following statements about large routing tables is incorrect?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Large routing tables are expensive in terms of memory requirements."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Large routing tables can create problems if they reach a router's assigned memory limits."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Large routing tables require more host IP addresses for each router."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Large routing tables create larger routing updates."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Large routing tables require more host IP addresses for each router.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q106",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "networks.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "To filter and limit traffic based upon application type."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "To manage routing updates traveling between autonomous systems."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "To provide packet replication for multicast services."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: To manage routing updates traveling between autonomous systems.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q107",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "What is a possible consequence when a loop forms?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "The router will close down all ports."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "The router will reset."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Packets will be delivered to random destinations."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Link saturation will occur."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Link saturation will occur.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q108",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "How does BGP solve the problem of exponential routing table growth?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "By restricting routing updates to certain parts of the day."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "By using dedicated massive memory arrays for routing tables."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "By restricting routing updates to only pre-determined routers."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Through route summarization between autonomous systems."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Through route summarization between autonomous systems.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q109",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "addresses with IP addresses.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "IP packets are encapsulated within Ethernet frames."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "IP packets are sent in an Ethernet frame variant using the IPoE protocol."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: IP packets are encapsulated within Ethernet frames.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q110",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "If a PC on a local area Ethernet network needs to communicate with a newly installed printer on the same Ethernet, how does it find the printer's Destination MAC address?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "The PC performs a DNS request."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "The PC checks its ARP table then issues an ARP request, if required."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "The PC sends a broadcast 'MAC_addr_help' message."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The PC searches its routing table."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: The PC checks its ARP table then issues an ARP request, if required.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q111",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "CSMA/CD stands for 'Carrier Sense Multiple Access with (...) Detection'. What is the missing word?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Checksum"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Combined"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Carrier"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Collision"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Collision."
    },
    {
      "id": "q112",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "What function does the Frame Check Sequence perform for Ethernet frames?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "It provides the ability to detect corrupted Ethernet frame data."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "It checks that all Ethernet frames are received in the correct sequence."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "It provides stateful security features.]"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "It checks that Ethernet-attached devices transmit in the correct order."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: It provides the ability to detect corrupted Ethernet frame data.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q113",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "At which layer in the TCP/IP model does Ethernet operate?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Network"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Link"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Transport"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Application"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Link."
    },
    {
      "id": "q114",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "What is another name for a default route?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "The gateway route"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "The worst case route"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "The zero address"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The default vector"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: The zero address."
    },
    {
      "id": "q115",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "ARP is a widely used communications protocol for ...?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "resolving routing table entries into longest matches."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "resolving network-layer IP addresses into link layer MAC addresses."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "resolving Ethernet contention issues."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "resolving Ethernet MAC address duplication conflicts."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: resolving network-layer IP addresses into link layer MAC addresses.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q116",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment — IP v4 Topology Considerations",
      "question": "Which standards body is responsible for the Ethernet main standard 802.3?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "IEEE"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "3GPP"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "IETF"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "CCITT"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: IEEE."
    },
    {
      "id": "q117",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Overview",
      "question": "Which statement is true about dual-stack routers?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Dual-stack routers can forward IPv4 and IPv6 packets simultaneously."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Dual-stack routers can forward IPv6 packets, but IPv4 packets must be encapsulated in"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Dual-stack routers can forward IPv4 and IPv6 packets simultaneously.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q118",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Overview",
      "question": "IPv6 directly enables a version of which routing protocol?",
      "multi": true,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "2^96 addresses"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "2^128 addresses"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "OSPF"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Segment Routing"
        },
        {
          "id": "E",
          "text": "IS-IS"
        },
        {
          "id": "F",
          "text": "BGP"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B",
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answers: 2^128 addresses; Segment Routing."
    },
    {
      "id": "q119",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Overview",
      "question": "Which protocol came between IPv4 and IPv6?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Packetized Voice Protocol"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Internet Stream Protocol"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Packetized Media Protocol"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Internet Service Protocol"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Internet Stream Protocol."
    },
    {
      "id": "q120",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Overview",
      "question": "Why is hexadecimal notation used in written IPv6 addresses?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Hexadecimal is easier to remember because all the characters are letters from the alphabet (A-Z)."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "It is the only format routers can manipulate with such large addresses."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Hexadecimal notation has replaced decimal notation for both IPv6 and IPv4 addresses."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "It makes the address shorter than using decimal or binary notation."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: It makes the address shorter than using decimal or binary notation.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q121",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Overview",
      "question": "How much larger is an IPv6 address compared with an IPv4 address?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "128 bits"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "96 bits"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "64 bits"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "32 bits"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 96 bits."
    },
    {
      "id": "q122",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Overview",
      "question": "What are the two main IPv4-to-IPv6 transition techniques?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Termination and transition"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Termination and translation"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Tunneling and transition"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Tunneling and translation"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Tunneling and translation."
    },
    {
      "id": "q123",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "A maximum of how many IPv6 addresses can be assigned to an IPv6 interface?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "One"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Two"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Three"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Three or more"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Three or more."
    },
    {
      "id": "q124",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "A minimum of how many bits of subnet address is required to represent 8 networks?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Two"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Three"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Four"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Eight"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Three."
    },
    {
      "id": "q125",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "An IPv6 address consists of how many bits?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "64"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "1028"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "2048"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "128"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 128."
    },
    {
      "id": "q126",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Why is colon-hexadecimal notation used instead of dotted-decimal notation for IPv6 address representation?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "To shorten addresses."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "It would not be possible to use dotted-decimal notation."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Because computers can interpret colon-hexadecimal more quickly."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Because colon-hexadecimal notation is easier to remember."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: To shorten addresses.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q127",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "In an IPv6 address, what does'::' (double colon) signify?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "A multicast address"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Zero compression"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "A loopback address"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Leading zero suppression"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Zero compression."
    },
    {
      "id": "q128",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Who directly supplies a company with an IPv6 Global routing prefix?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "The company buys one from a public auction of available address space."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "An Internet Service Provider."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "A local Internet registry."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The Internet Assigned Numbers Authority."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: An Internet Service Provider.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q129",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "How is '1101' (binary) represented in hexadecimal notation?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "e"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "b"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "d"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "a"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: d."
    },
    {
      "id": "q130",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which of the following is not a legitimate way to represent the following IPv6 address? 2001:0db8:140c:8000:0000:00d0:0000:140f",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "2001:db8:140c::d0::140f"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "2001:0db8:140c:0:0:00d0:0:140f"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "2001:db8:140c::d0:0000:140f"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "2001:db8:140c::d0:0:140f"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 2001:db8:140c::d0::140f."
    },
    {
      "id": "q131",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which part of an IPv6 destination address does an IPv6 router use to make a forwarding decision for a received IPv6 packet?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Destination port"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Interface ID"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Routing ID"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Routing prefix"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Routing prefix."
    },
    {
      "id": "q132",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Unique local unicast addresses can be used to provide what?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Private addressing."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Loopback addresses."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Multicast communication with all Interface IDs on a local network."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Auto-configuration."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Private addressing.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q133",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What dictates the use of IPv6 address space?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "There are no strict standards, just recommendations."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "International Telecommunication Union standards."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Internet Engineering Task Force standards."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Agreements between the telecom industry's major vendors."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Internet Engineering Task Force standards.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q134",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which is the largest possible IPv4 or IPv6 packet header?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "20bytes"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "40 bytes"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "60 bytes"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "82bytes"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 60 bytes."
    },
    {
      "id": "q135",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which of the following is a legitimate reason to reduce the number of header fields from IPv4 to IPv6?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Fewer header fields means reduced processing for routing nodes."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "IPv6 has a reduced set of possible applications than IPv4."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Advanced routers can no longer handle more than 8 fields because of the Application"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Fewer header fields means reduced processing for routing nodes.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q136",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which Extension Header must appear first if more than one is used in a chain?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Authentication"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Destination Options"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Fragment"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Hop-by-Hop Options"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Hop-by-Hop Options."
    },
    {
      "id": "q137",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which two fields comprise 80% of the IPv6 packet header?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Source and Destination Addresses"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Traffic Class and Header Checksum"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Flow Label and Payload Length"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Options and Padding"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Source and Destination Addresses."
    },
    {
      "id": "q138",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which IPv6 header characteristic helps to improve overall forwarding performance?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Simplicity"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Feature richness"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Flexibility"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Traffic Class field"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Simplicity."
    },
    {
      "id": "q139",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Each Extension Header must be a multiple of how many octets/bytes?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "8"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "16"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "24"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "32"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 8."
    },
    {
      "id": "q140",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "How does IPv6 cater for the functionality that was previously included in the IPv4 'Options' field?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "IPv6 doesn't permit the use of options."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "IPv6 has an Extension Header type called 'Options'."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "IPv6uses one or more Extension Headers."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "IPv6 includes an Options field in the IPv6 Main Header."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: IPv6uses one or more Extension Headers.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q141",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What is one of the biggest differences between stateless and stateful address autoconfiguration?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "No DNS server is required."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Stateful address autoconfiguration requires no database administration."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "No DHCP server is required."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Only one of them is supported by IPv6."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: No DHCP server is required.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q142",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Neighbor Discovery Protocol is supported by messages from which other protocol?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "SMTP"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "BGP"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "ICMP"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "UDP"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: ICMP."
    },
    {
      "id": "q143",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which of the following is not a Neighbor Discovery Protocol application?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Address resolution"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Address autoconfiguration"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Routing update generation"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Prefix discovery"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Routing update generation."
    },
    {
      "id": "q144",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which is one of the main benefits of IPv6 autoconfiguration?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Reduced operational costs."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Reduced round-trip delays."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Greater throughput."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Reduced capital expenditure."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Reduced operational costs.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q145",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "When the 'EUI-64 interface identifier' is used to create IPv6 addresses, what is the address created upon?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Another IPv6 address already issued to the same node."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "A pseudo-random number generator using '64' as a seed."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "A pseudo-random number generated from the time of day."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The interface's MAC address."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: The interface's MAC address.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q146",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "How does an IPv6 host find its local network prefix?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "The host sends a broadcast message soliciting help."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "The host can deduce its network prefix from its Link-local address."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "The host sends a 'Router Solicitation' ICMPv6 message to its local router."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The host sends a 'Prefix Solicitation' ICMPv6 message to its local router."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: The host sends a 'Router Solicitation' ICMPv6 message to its local router.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q147",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Why are DNSv6 resource records called 'AAAA'?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Because IPv6 addresses are four times as long as IPv4 addresses."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "It relates to the format of the records which have four fields, each starting with an 'A'."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Because 'AAAA' would be the first record alphanumerically."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "It relates to the name of the address look-up algorithm."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Because IPv6 addresses are four times as long as IPv4 addresses.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q148",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What are the two types of ICMP messages?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Control and status"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Error and informational"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Error and statistic"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Control and event"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Error and informational."
    },
    {
      "id": "q149",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What type of protocol is IS-IS?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Link state"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Static state"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Distance vector"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Path vector"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Link state."
    },
    {
      "id": "q150",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "IS-IS is used to exchange routing information.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "True"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "False"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: True."
    },
    {
      "id": "q151",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which protocol family does IS-IS belong to?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "SDH/Sonet"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "ISO/OSI"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "TCP/IP"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "IPX/SPX"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: ISO/OSI."
    },
    {
      "id": "q152",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What is true about Integrated IS-IS?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "It supports routing for both IP and ISO/OSI protocols"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "It provides an integrated network management solution"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "It integrates the best features of IS-IS and OSPF"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "It integrates routing and bridging within one router"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: It supports routing for both IP and ISO/OSI protocols."
    },
    {
      "id": "q153",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "In which environment can IS-IS be deployed? (Choose 3)",
      "multi": true,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Pure TCP"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Dual OSI and IP"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Pure OSI"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Pure IP"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B",
        "C",
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answers: Dual OSI and IP; Pure OSI; Pure IP."
    },
    {
      "id": "q154",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "A router needs to build a routing table before it can forward traffic.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "True"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "False"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: True."
    },
    {
      "id": "q155",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which are true statements about ISO/OSI protocols? (Choose 2)",
      "multi": true,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "They have been used to manage telecommunication equipment"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "They area subset of TCP/IP"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "They area superset of TCP/IP"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "They were supposed to replace TCP/IP"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A",
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answers: They have been used to manage telecommunication equipment; They were supposed to replace TCP/IP."
    },
    {
      "id": "q156",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What does a Level-1 IS router do? (Choose two)",
      "multi": true,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Exchange routing information between areas"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Sends packets destined for a different area to the closest Level 1/2 IS in its own area"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Keeps track of the topology changes within its own area"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Maintains topology of the whole network in a multi-area environment"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B",
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answers: Sends packets destined for a different area to the closest Level 1/2 IS in its own area; Keeps track of the topology changes within its own area."
    },
    {
      "id": "q157",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Select the most probable cause of suboptimal routing in IS-IS networks",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Faulty SPF calculation"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Too many hops included ina path"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Default path selection based on attached bit"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Incorrect interface speed recognition"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Default path selection based on attached bit."
    },
    {
      "id": "q158",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What is the SPF calculation based on for IS-IS?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Metric assigned to links"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Speed of links"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Number of routers in a path"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Metric assigned to links."
    },
    {
      "id": "q159",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What is true about a Level 2 router? (Choose three)",
      "multi": true,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Knows the topology of its own area"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Is a backbone router"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "So Can have neighbors in the same and different areas"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Contains both a Level 1 and Level 2 link-state database"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B",
        "C",
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answers: Is a backbone router; So Can have neighbors in the same and different areas; Contains both a Level 1 and Level 2 link-state database."
    },
    {
      "id": "q160",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Select the 3 major components of an NSAP used in IP networks (Select three).",
      "multi": true,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "HO-DSP"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "AFI + area"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "SEL"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "IDI"
        },
        {
          "id": "E",
          "text": "System ID"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B",
        "C",
        "E"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answers: AFI + area; SEL; System ID."
    },
    {
      "id": "q161",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "How many DIS''es can be elected in a single L1 area?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "l"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "2"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "3"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Unlimited number"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Unlimited number."
    },
    {
      "id": "q162",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which statement is true regarding suboptimal routing in IS-IS networks?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "It can happen when routing within an L2 area"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "It can't happen at all"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "It can happen when routing within an L1 area"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "It can happen when routing between areas"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: It can happen when routing between areas."
    },
    {
      "id": "q163",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which router will a Level 1 router choose when it needs to send a packet destined fora different area?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "It chooses the closest Level 1 or Level 2 router in the area (based on path cost)."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "It chooses the Level 1 or Level 2 router having the shortest path to the destination."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "It chooses the router with the lowest administrative distance."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "It chooses the Level 1 router having the shortest path to the destination."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: It chooses the Level 1 router having the shortest path to the destination.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q164",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What information can be found in an LSP? (Choose two)",
      "multi": true,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Default gateway configured for the originating IS"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Neighbors in the originating IS"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Networks connected to the originating IS"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "A List of networks existing in the given area"
        },
        {
          "id": "E",
          "text": "Link state database"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C",
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answers: Networks connected to the originating IS; A List of networks existing in the given area."
    },
    {
      "id": "q165",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "All IS-IS routers within the same area must have the same topology database.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "False"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "True"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: True."
    },
    {
      "id": "q166",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "A Level 1 router can have adjacent neighbors in a different area.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "False"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "True"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: False."
    },
    {
      "id": "q167",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "How do IS routers learn a network topology?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Byrunning the SPF algorithm"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "By examining content of received LSPs"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Through hello packets received from the neighbors"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Through static configuration provisioned by a network administrator"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: By examining content of received LSPs."
    },
    {
      "id": "q168",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "IS systems are considered neighbors when:",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "They are directly connected"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "They both received hello messages confirming neighbor status"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "They both received hello messages from each other"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "They belong to the same area"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: They both received hello messages confirming neighbor status."
    },
    {
      "id": "q169",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Routing between different areas refers to which level of routing?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Level 0"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Level 1"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Level 2"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Level 3"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Level 2."
    },
    {
      "id": "q170",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What challenge does broadcast network present from the topology perspective?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Broadcast segments are seen as a star by outside systems"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Broadcast segments are seen as a full mesh by outside systems"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Broadcast networks don't allow for DIS deployment"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Broadcast segments generate too much control traffic"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Broadcast segments generate too much control traffic."
    },
    {
      "id": "q171",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which are IS-IS router types? (Choose three)",
      "multi": true,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Level 1/2"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Level 1"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Level 2"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Level 3"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A",
        "B",
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answers: Level 1/2; Level 1; Level 2."
    },
    {
      "id": "q172",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "An L1/L2 router maintains two separate IP routing tables.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "False"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "True"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: False."
    },
    {
      "id": "q173",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "An L1/L2 router maintains two separate link state databases.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "True"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "False"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: True."
    },
    {
      "id": "q174",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What is true about a Level 1 router?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "It is a backbone router"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "It contains both a Level 1 and a Level 2 link-state database"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "It can have Level 1 and Level 2 adjacent neighbors"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "It knows the topology only of its own area"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: It knows the topology only of its own area."
    },
    {
      "id": "q175",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which action or actions can a Label Edge Router (LER) perform?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Push"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Swap"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Pop"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Pop and push"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Pop and push."
    },
    {
      "id": "q176",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which is another common name for an MPLS header?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Addition header"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "In-between header"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Shim header"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Cartridge header"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Shim header."
    },
    {
      "id": "q177",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What do MPLS labels identify?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Established paths between endpoints"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "The best path from customer edge to customer edge"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "The paths with the lowest cost"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The LSRs with the least downtime"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Established paths between endpoints."
    },
    {
      "id": "q178",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What is the purpose of Differentiated Services or DiffServ?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "It can prioritize which LER or LSR that shall transmit a data packet"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "It enables comparisons between LSPs just like Open Shortest Path First (OSPF)"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "It is used for prioritization purposes"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "It adds MPLS labels to identify VPNs"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: It is used for prioritization purposes."
    },
    {
      "id": "q179",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What are routers that operate at the edge of MPLS networks called?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Label Edge Router (LER)"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "MPLS Edge Router (MER)"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Label Push and Pop Router (LPPR)"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "MPLS Entry and Exit Router (LEER)"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Label Edge Router (LER)."
    },
    {
      "id": "q180",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "At which layer in the OSI model is MPLS said to operate?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Layer1"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Layer 2"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Layer 2.5"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Layer3"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Layer 2.5."
    },
    {
      "id": "q181",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What kind of data can MPLS carry?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Voice"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Video"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Any unencrypted data"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "All the above and more"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: All the above and more."
    },
    {
      "id": "q182",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What does the Traffic Class field in an MPLS label identify?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "The QoS priority"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "The class of the MPLS path"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "The type of Layer 3 protocol"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The payload class"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: The QoS priority."
    },
    {
      "id": "q183",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "MPLS inserts an MPLS header in packets. What is the most common mode for how this is done?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Frame mode"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Asynchronous transfer mode"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Frame mode."
    },
    {
      "id": "q184",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Where is the MPLS header located in a packet that contains a Layer 2 header and a payload header?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Before the Layer 2 header"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Right of the Layer 2 header"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "After the payload"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "After the Layer 3 header"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Right of the Layer 2 header."
    },
    {
      "id": "q185",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What do MPLS labels identify?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "The paths with the lowest cost"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Established paths between endpoints"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "The best path from customer edge to customer edge"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The LSRs with the least downtime"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Established paths between endpoints."
    },
    {
      "id": "q186",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What is one router type in an MPLS network called?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Label Switch Router (LSR)"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Label Swap Router (LSR)"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Label Switcher (LS)"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "MPLS Switch Router (MSR)"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Label Switch Router (LSR)."
    },
    {
      "id": "q187",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What kind of data can MPLS carry?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Voice"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Video"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Any unencrypted data"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "All the above and more"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: All the above and more."
    },
    {
      "id": "q188",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Can MPLS carry data for circuit-based networks and packet-switched networks?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Yes, unless it is duplex traffic"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "No, only for circuit-based networks"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "No, only for packet-switched networks"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Yes."
    },
    {
      "id": "q189",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "How many Label Switch Paths (LSPs) does duplex traffic require?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "1"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "2"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "4"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "8"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 2."
    },
    {
      "id": "q190",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which descriptions match (1) Convergence-based resilience and (2) Fast Reroute (FRR)?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "(1) Passive handling with recalculation and (2) fast handling with recalculation"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "(1) Reactive handling with recalculation and (2) proactive handling with pre-calculation"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "(1) Proactive handling with recalculation and (2) inactive handling with pre-calculation"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: (1) Reactive handling with recalculation and (2) proactive handling with pre-calculation."
    },
    {
      "id": "q191",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "At which layer in the OSI model do LDP and RSVP-TE operate?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Network layer"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Session layer"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Transport layer"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Data Link layer"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Transport layer."
    },
    {
      "id": "q192",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which label distribution mode or modes are available for RSVP-TE?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Downstream on Demand"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Downstream on Demand and Unsolicited Downstream"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Unsolicited Downstream"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Ordered and Independent Control"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Downstream on Demand."
    },
    {
      "id": "q193",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "For RSVP-TE, where is a description of the LSP stored?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "In an Explicit Route Object (ERO) in all routers along the LSP"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "In a Little Fast Information Base in all MPLS routers"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "In an Explicit Route Object (ERO) in the ingress and egress routers only"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "In the shim header of each packet"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: In an Explicit Route Object (ERO) in all routers along the LSP."
    },
    {
      "id": "q194",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which protocol selects the path to activate as an LSP?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "LDP"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "The IGP"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "BGP"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "LDP and the IGP through a negotiation"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: The IGP."
    },
    {
      "id": "q195",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which is the main difference between LDP and RSVP-TE?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "RSVP-TE provides greater control over LSPs"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "LDP provides greater control over LSPs"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "LDP has a higher operational overhead"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "RSVP-TE is less flexible"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: RSVP-TE provides greater control over LSPs."
    },
    {
      "id": "q196",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Based on what does RSVP-TE select a Label Switched Path (LSP)?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "The automatically generated BGP path"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "The shortest path"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "A manually defined Forwarding Equivalence Class (FEC)"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "The RFC with the highest number"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: A manually defined Forwarding Equivalence Class (FEC)."
    },
    {
      "id": "q197",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "For every network prefix in the FIB, LDP in the Label Edge Routers (LERs) and Label Switch Routers (LSRs) binds FECs to...?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Interfaces"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Labels"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "LSPs"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Other FECs"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Labels."
    },
    {
      "id": "q198",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Which area plays the main role in the OSPF concept?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Backbone"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Level 1 area"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Autonomous System"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Area 1"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Backbone."
    },
    {
      "id": "q199",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "The routing table is required by router in order to forward traffic.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "True"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "False"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: True."
    },
    {
      "id": "q200",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What type of protocol is OSPF?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Distance vector"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Link state"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Routed protocol"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Path vector"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Link state."
    },
    {
      "id": "q201",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "All areas must be connected to the Backbone area.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "True"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "False"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: True."
    },
    {
      "id": "q202",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "What are the reasons to divide one large network into multiple smaller areas? (Choose 2)",
      "multi": true,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "It increases the number of routing recalculations in the routing database."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "It reduces the number of routing recalculations in the routing database."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "It increases the total number of possible connected subscribers."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "It makes all changes inside any area invisible for all other areas ."
        },
        {
          "id": "E",
          "text": "It simplifies the architecture of the network."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B",
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answers: It reduces the number of routing recalculations in the routing database.; It makes all changes inside any area invisible for all other areas .."
    },
    {
      "id": "q203",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Choose the true statement.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "OSPF is used to exchange routing information and calculate best paths to all sources."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "OSPF is used to exchange routing information and calculate best paths to all destinations."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "OSPF is used to forward data between sources and destinations."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: OSPF is used to exchange routing information and calculate best paths to all destinations.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q204",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "In the OSPF there are different roles routers can perform.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "True"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "False"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: True."
    },
    {
      "id": "q205",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - IPv6 Addressing",
      "question": "Area Border Router is the router which :",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Connects one or more areas to the Backbone Area."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Represents the multi-access network and its attached routers to the rest of the OSPF area."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Whose interfaces belong to the same area."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Connects one or more areas to the Backbone Area.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q206",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Which area plays the main role in the OSPF concept?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Backbone"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Level 1 area"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Autonomous System"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Area 1"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Backbone."
    },
    {
      "id": "q207",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "In a broadcast network, OSPF routers form adjacencies with which of the following?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "DR"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Adjacent router"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Next hop router"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Peer router"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: DR."
    },
    {
      "id": "q208",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Choose the Link-State Advertisements from the list (Choose three).",
      "multi": true,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Router LSA"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Network LSA"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Summary LSA"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "AS Boundary Router Summary LSA"
        },
        {
          "id": "E",
          "text": "AS External LSA"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A",
        "B",
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answers: Router LSA; Network LSA; Summary LSA."
    },
    {
      "id": "q209",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "BDR stands for:",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Bidirectional DR"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Backup DR"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Boundary DR"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Backup DR."
    },
    {
      "id": "q210",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Each Autonomous Boundary Router (ABR) must have at least one interface connected to the Backbone Area.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "True"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "False"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: True."
    },
    {
      "id": "q211",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Choose the Backbone Area.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "0.0.0.0"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "0.0.0.1"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "224.0.0.0"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "224.0.0.1"
        },
        {
          "id": "E",
          "text": "224.0.0.4"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: 0.0.0.0."
    },
    {
      "id": "q212",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "In the OSPF there are different types of routers.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "True"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "False"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: True."
    },
    {
      "id": "q213",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "OSPF uses TCP as a transport protocol.",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "True"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "False"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: False."
    },
    {
      "id": "q214",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Which is a security principle from the CIA Triad?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Integrity"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Identification"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Indemnity"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Information"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Integrity."
    },
    {
      "id": "q215",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Working with the CIA Triad usually requires...",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "prioritizing the Triad principles in their order (C-I-A)."
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "balancing the Triad principles."
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "making sure to meet all Triad principles fully."
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "choosing one of the principles according to business objectives."
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: balancing the Triad principles.."
    },
    {
      "id": "q216",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Which is the concept of controlling what a user can do after they are allowed access to a system?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Authentication"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Auditing"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Accounting"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Authorization"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Accounting."
    },
    {
      "id": "q217",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Which risk treatment involves buying insurance or outsourcing the risk to another organization?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Risk Avoidance"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Risk Transference"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Risk Collection"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Risk Acceptance"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Risk Transference."
    },
    {
      "id": "q218",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "What is a weakness that could be exploited by a threat called?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "A risk"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "A breach"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "A vulnerability"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "An asset"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: A vulnerability."
    },
    {
      "id": "q219",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Safeguards are also known as....?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Counterparts"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Controls"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Capacities"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Capabilities"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "B"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Controls."
    },
    {
      "id": "q220",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "What is the concept that a user cannot deny that they performed an action on a system called?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Non-repudiation"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Non-discriminatory"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Non-interference"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Non-redundancy"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Non-repudiation."
    },
    {
      "id": "q221",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Standards relating to the specification of the IPsec protocol are published by whom?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "IETF and 3GPP"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "3GPP"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "IETF"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "IEEE"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: IETF."
    },
    {
      "id": "q222",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Which of the following are both true statements about Transport mode compared with Tunnel mode?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Transport mode produces smaller packets, Tunnel mode is more secure"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Transport mode produces smaller packets, Tunnel mode is less secure"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Transport mode produces larger packets, Tunnel mode is less secure"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Transport mode produces larger packets, Tunnel mode is more secure"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Transport mode produces smaller packets, Tunnel mode is more secure."
    },
    {
      "id": "q223",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Pre-Shared Key (PSK) takes the form of ___",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "An electronic chip device containing a secure ID"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "A certificate generated by the device vendor"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "A pseudo-random numeric sequence generated as a software toke"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "A text string, entered manually by an administrator"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: A text string, entered manually by an administrator."
    },
    {
      "id": "q224",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Which one of the following statements about Child SAs is true?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Child SAs are established before the IKE SA"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Child SAs are related to one or more IKE SAs"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Child SAs are renewed typically every 24 hours"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Child SAs are created in unidirectional pairs"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "D"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Child SAs are created in unidirectional pairs."
    },
    {
      "id": "q225",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "IPsec sits at which layer of the OSI stack?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Three (Network layer)"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Two (Data link layer)"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Four (Transport layer)"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Five (Session layer)"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Three (Network layer)."
    },
    {
      "id": "q226",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Which statement is correct about an IPsec VPN?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "An IPsec VPN exists between two IPsec peers"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "An IPsec VPN is always secured by Pre-Shared Keys"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "An IPsec VPN only exists when IPsec is used in transport mode"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "An IPsec VPN consists of one Child SA pair"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: An IPsec VPN exists between two IPsec peers."
    },
    {
      "id": "q227",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "ESP provides encryption and authentication, AH provides what?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Authentication only"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Encryption only"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Encryption and authentication"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "None of the above"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "A"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Authentication only."
    },
    {
      "id": "q228",
      "section": "Knowledge Assessment - OSPF Fundamentals",
      "question": "Secure keys are used for what?",
      "multi": false,
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Traffic protection and outer header calculation"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Peer authentication only"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Traffic protection and peer authentication"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Traffic protection only"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [
        "C"
      ],
      "explanation": "Correct answer: Traffic protection and peer authentication."
    }
  ]
}